Databases 2
Project 1
Brady Snowden
James Taylor

To build the database using our ExtendedSimpleDB, run the main method of Startup.java in src.simpledb.server. This method should be run with two arguments. The first is the file path at which the database should be built. The second should be a string specifying which replacement policy to build into the database. The main options for this second argument are "LRU" and "Clock", but any other string will build the database using a FIFO policy.